

DATOS DE CONTACTO

Celular: (+54) 9 2477 595326

Correo: francoaugustoacosta@gmail.com

Portfolio: ffran-acosta.netlify.app

LinkedIn: @ffran-acosta GitHub: ffran-acosta

Localidad: Pergamino, Buenos Aires,

Argentina

PERFIL PERSONAL

Me llamo Franco, tengo 27 años y me gradué recientemente como Desarrollador Web en Digital House. Soy una persona proactiva con ganas de seguir aprendiendo nuevas tecnologías y me siento a gusto trabajando tanto en el frontend, como en el backend.

SKILLS

JavaSctipt
Python

Patrón de

React

Java

arquitectura

NodeJS

SOL

MVC

Express

• GIT

Postman

TypeScript • Sequelize • Creacion y

Metodolgías consumo de

HTML

ágiles -

APIs

CSS EJS

Scrum

FORTALEZAS

- Personalidad Proactiva
- · Resolución de problemas
- Adaptación a equipos de trabajo existentes
- · Capacidad de liderazgo
- · Excelentes relaciones interpersonales
- Alta captación de aprendizaje
- · Dedicación y compromiso
- Autocritico
- · Carnet de conducir (nacional)

FRANCO ACOSTA

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCIA PROFESIONAL

RUTH SAGER: website (03/2023)

Como freelance estoy actualmente desarrollando la wabsite en React de Ruth Sager.

Contacto: Eugenio Berasain (02474-15404883)

OXIGENO: e-commerce (06/2022 - 12/2022)

Como parte del equipo de desarrollo, me desempeñé como desarrollador full stack en OXIGENO, un e-commerce asignado como proyecto integrador en la edtech Digital House. Con la técnica de desarrollo scrum el proyecto fue realizado en NodeJs utilizando tecnologías como HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Express, MySql, Sequelize, Git entre otras.

Editor (2022)

Me desempeño actualmente editando fotos y videos con el pack Creative Cloud de Adobe para la productora Muzzo Visions, Miami, Florida, USA. Contacto: Nicolás Muzzioli (+1) 214 4860673

Venta de Hardware y reparación de pc (2020 - 2022)

Elaboración de presupuesto, armados, reparación y reacondicionamiento de PC y notebook. (Emprendimiento)

RUTH SAGER (11/2017 - 9-2020)

Industria alimenticia. Durante el primer año desempeñándome en la elaboración, envasado y preparación para distribución del producto. Durante el segundo periodo en área administrativa.

Contacto: Eugenio Berasain (02474-15404883)

FORMACION ACADEMICA

DIGITAL HOUSE

- Programación Web Full Stack, 2022

UNNOBA Pergamino

- Lic. en Sistemas 2018/21

UTN Rosario

- Ingeniería en Sistemas 2017

UNR

- Lic. Psicología 2014/16

IDIOMAS

ESPAÑOL - Nativo

INGLES - Avanzado

8 años Instituto KEN



DATOS DE CONTACTO

Phone: (+54) 9 2477 595326

Correo: francoaugustoacosta@gmail.com

Portfolio: ffran-acosta.netlify.app

LinkedIn: <u>@ffran-acosta</u> GitHub: <u>ffran-acosta</u>

Location: Pergamino, Buenos Aires,

Argentina

PERFIL PERSONAL

My name is Franco, I am 27 years old and I recently graduated as a Full Stack Web Developer at Digital House. I am a proactive person with a desire to continue learning new technologies and I feel comfortable working both on the frontend and backend.

SKILLS

JavaSctipt • Python

Java

• GIT

Scrum

MVC
(Model-

• React • .

`.

NodeJS

SQL view-

Express

_...

controller)

• TypeScript • Sequelize

Postman

HTMLCSS

methodology consumption

Creation and

• EJS

of APIs

STRENGTHS

- Proactive personality
- · Problem-solving skills
- · Adaptability to existing work teams
- · Leadership ability
- · Excellent interpersonal relationships
- High learning ability
- · Dedication and commitment
- Self-critical
- National driver's license

FRANCO ACOSTA

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

RUTH SAGER: website (03/2023)

As a freelancer, I am currently developing Ruth Sager's React website. Contact: Eugenio Berasain (02474-15404883)

OXIGENO: e-commerce (06/2022 - 12/2022)

As part of the development team, I worked as a *full-stack web developer* at OXIGENO, an e-commerce assigned as an integrative project in the edtech *Digital House*. Using the scrum development technique, the project was completed using NodeJs and technologies such as *HTML*, *CSS*, *JavaScript*, *React*, *Express*, *MySql*, *Sequelize*, *Git*, *among others*.

Editor (2022)

I am currently working on editing photos and videos using the Adobe Creative Cloud pack for the production company Muzzo Visions, Miami, Florida, USA.

Reference: Nicolás Muzzioli (+1) 214 4860673

Sale of hardware and PC repair (2020 - 2022)

Budget preparation, assembly, repair, and refurbishment of PC and laptops. (Entrepreneurship)

RUTH SAGER (11/2017 - 9-2020)

Food industry. During the first year, I worked in the production, packaging, and preparation for distribution of the product. During the second period in the administrative area, I developed a system for stock control, quality control, and distribution.

Reference: Eugenio Berasain (02474-15404883)

EDUCATION

DIGITAL HOUSE

- Full Stack Web Developer, 2022

UNNOBA Pergamino

- Bachelor of Systems 2018/21

UTN Rosario

- Systems Engineering 2017

UNR

- Degree in Psychology 2014/16

LANGUAGES

SPANISH - Native

ENGLISH - Advanced 8 years at KEN Institute